chimebank.com 2019-06-20

# Privacy Policy - Chime Banking

Rev. 08/2017

FACTS: | What Does The Bancorp Do With Your Personal Information?  
---|---  
Why? | Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some, but not all, sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.  
What? | The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include: 

  * Social Security Number and income
  * Account balances and transaction history
  * Credit history and credit scores

When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information, as described in this notice.  
  
How? | All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal information; the reasons The Bancorp chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.  
  
### Reasons We Can Share Your Personal Information

| 

### Does The Bancorp share?

| 

### Can you limit this sharing?  
  
---|---|---  
For our everyday business purposes — Such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus | Yes | No  
For our marketing purposes — To offer our products and services to you | Yes | No  
For joint marketing with other financial companies | No | We don’t share  
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes — Information about your transactions and experiences | No | We don’t share  
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes — Information about your creditworthiness | No | We don’t share  
For nonaffiliates to market to you | Yes | Yes  
  
> ### To limit our sharing:
> 
>   * Login to your account at [www.chimebank.com](https://www.chimebank.com/) or via the Chime Mobile application to update your Privacy Settings.
> 

> 
> **Please note:**  If you are a  _new_  customer, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the date we sent this notice. When you are  _no longer_  our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.
> 
> However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.

> ### Questions?
> 
> Call us, toll-free, at (844) 244-6363, email us at [support@chimebank.com](mailto:support@chimebank.com), or visit us at [www.chimebank.com](https://www.chimebank.com/).

### Who we are

Who is providing this notice? | This notice is provided by the business units of The Bancorp, Inc., and its affiliates, including, but no limited to, The Bancorp Bank, Bancorp Card Services, Inc., and TBBK Direct Leasing, LLC.  
---|---  
  
### What We Do

How does The Bancorp protect my personal information? | To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.  
We also limit access to information to those employees for whom access is necessary.  
---|---  
How does The Bancorp collect my personal information? | We collect your personal information when, for example, you: 

  * open an account or pay your bills
  * make deposits or withdrawals from your account or give us your contact information
  * provide account information

We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.  
  
Why can’t I limit all sharing? | Federal law gives you the right to limit only: 

  * sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes – information about your creditworthiness
  * affiliates from using your information to market to you
  * sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you

State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing. See below for more on your rights under state law.  
  
### Definitions

Affiliates | 

Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.

  * _Our affiliates include financial companies such as The Bancorp Bank, Bancorp Card Services, Inc., and TBBK Direct Leasing, LLC._

---|---  
Nonaffiliates | 

Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.

  * _Nonaffiliates we share with can include online payment companies, direct marketing companies and prepaid card providers._

Joint marketing | 

A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.

  * _The Bancorp does not jointly market._

> ### Other important information
> 
> *California Residents — In accordance with California law, we will not share information we collect about you with companies outside of Chime or The Bancorp, unless the law allows.  For example, we may share information with your consent, to service your accounts, or to provide rewards or benefits you are entitled to. We will limit sharing around our companies to the extent required by California law.
> 
> *Vermont Residents — In accordance with Vermont law, we will not share personal financial information about you, other than transaction experience information, with other Bancorp companies or affiliates, nor will we share any personal financial information about you with other Bancorp companies for marketing purposes.
> 
> *Nevada Residents — We are providing you this notice pursuant to state law. You may be placed on our internal Do Not Call List by following the directions in the To limit direct marketing contact section. Nevada law requires that we also provide you with the following contact information: Bureau of Consumer Protection, Office of the Nevada Attorney General, 555 E. Washington St., Suite 3900, Las Vegas, NV 89101; Phone number- [702.486.3132](tel:17024863132); email: [BCPINFO@ag.state.nv.us](mailto:BCPINFO@ag.state.nv.us).
